<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on ceedon.io</title>
    <link>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on ceedon.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 11:10:36 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashling Homebrew Setting</title>
      <link>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/aisling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 11:10:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/aisling/</guid>
      <description>Towards the end of the lore-crafting Microscope session, it became apparent that a repository of information about the world would be incredibly beneficial for continuity. That repo will live here. It&amp;rsquo;s public, but hopefully unfound.
It&amp;rsquo;s extremely unlikely that I&amp;rsquo;ll atively share the whole with my players, but I will certainly source it to provide information gradients across the characters. This idea is straight-up stolen from an idea shared on the DnD subReddit that I thought was an elegant way to generate some intrigue and player engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morning</title>
      <link>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/morning/</guid>
      <description>This won&amp;rsquo;t be literary gold, but I&amp;rsquo;m writing it down. Something about morning makes it easier to do so. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s that I haven&amp;rsquo;t had time to spend too much time inside my head since returning from the clouds of dream. Note to self: check w/ Morpheus.
Early morning and late night share so much. The ones I&amp;rsquo;m speaking to are quiet, solitary things&amp;mdash;free from the myriad stimulae of life&amp;mdash;when you are left alone to ponder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press</title>
      <link>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/press/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/press/</guid>
      <description>Measure and grind beans.
Let bloom, then steep for seven.
Press, savor, and smile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starbucks Coldbrew</title>
      <link>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/starbucks-coldbrew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/starbucks-coldbrew/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s coldbrew with their beans. Surprising, I know.
Low acidity. Full bodied. No floral notes. Acrid even to my tastes.
Almost exactly what you would expect. Homogenization 4tW?
They steep for 12 hours. The beans are a blend specifically for this use. /shrug They leave the result as concentrate, so you get to pick the viscosity.
Honestly, a decent cup of coffee if you want your choice of strength virtually anywhere and quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So long, Stuttgart!</title>
      <link>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/so-long-stuttgart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/so-long-stuttgart/</guid>
      <description>So now that I&amp;rsquo;m comfortable with Stuttgart&amp;rsquo;s public transit system, it&amp;rsquo;s time to go.
I&amp;rsquo;m catching a train to Cologne and my first real airbnb experience—never seeing or speaking to your host disqualifies my previous one, amirite? I&amp;rsquo;m really looking forward to it. Hopefully my host will be as outgoing as she comes across and I might have her+her SO&amp;rsquo;s company while exploring. The more the merrier. My one gripe is being alone the majority of the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultra Traaaaain</title>
      <link>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/ultra-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/ultra-train/</guid>
      <description>I was promised connectivity. Promised. squints angrily You lied to me.
TIL: Building docker images that pull from Github without a connection is hard. We shall agree not to speak of gems.
It&amp;rsquo;s amazing to me that a country this densely populated can have SO MUCH empty space.
It&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;urbanized&amp;rdquo;—by which I mean people live in cities—but not like you think. It tends to be little pockets of civilization. Small towns super close to each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BA2626</title>
      <link>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/ba2626/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/ba2626/</guid>
      <description>Shepard&amp;rsquo;s Pie: mashed potatoes, peas, carrots, and some balefire-sloppyjoe-meat hybrid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London</title>
      <link>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/london/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/london/</guid>
      <description>Not going to make it out of the airport from the looks of it. Spent too much time trying to get my phone and card working, and moving through security is non-trivial.
At any rate, this will give me some time to fiddle with posts. And grab some potato quality pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World!</title>
      <link>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/rehello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceedon.github.io/blog/post/rehello-world/</guid>
      <description>A new incarnation of a blog, a vacation in Europe, a sea-change in work and life upon return: this post is the herald of all of these things.
The blog I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing an increasing amount on paper, so let&amp;rsquo;s do the Interwebs too! Do I have anything groundbreaking to say? Almost certainly not, but maybe some of you can learn from my struggles be they human or technical in nature.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>